https://www.limitedpapers.com/privacypolicy.html

Login/Register My Account
Items In Cart
$0.00
800.797.7022
Free shipping on all orders over $189!
Price: $0.00
Shipping:
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy for Limited Papers LTD Inc. (hereinafter referred to as “Limited Papers”) this privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for LimitedPapers.com. This privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Your privacy is top priority to us. When you shop at LimitedPapers.com and place your orders exclusively through LimitedPapers.com, all personal information that you share with us is kept absolutely private.
What Information do we collect?
We collect two types of information about our visitors: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site.
Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. Personal information is requested when you order a product or service, request a service or email newsletter, and send us feedback. For example, this information might include your name, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other payment information, and product details. With this information, LimitedPapers.com can fill your orders and better provide you with personalized services.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you shop on our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. For example, this information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet, browse and shop.
How we use the information?
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide LimitedPapers.com visitors with a superior customized online experience. We use the customer contact information to fill orders, contact purchasers to inform them of their order status, to send promotional information, to enhance the operation of our site and administer our systems.
Use of Cookies:
When you use our site we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to LimitedPapers.com. The cookies make your use of the site easier, allow you to retrieve an earlier shopping cart, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You will be unable to shop on our site without your browser set to accept cookies.
How to update or correct your Information?
We believe you should have the ability to access and edit the personal information that you have provided to us. During the online ordering process you can review, change, or delete the information that you have submitted. You may change any of your personal information in your account online at any time. We encourage you to promptly update your information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed.
Keeping your information private:
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Marketing:
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via postal mail or email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy Policy. You may opt out from our e-mail listings or of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website.
What if we change our privacy Policy?
This Privacy Policy was last changed on Mar 1, 2007. If LimitedPapers.com makes changes to any terms or conditions of the Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted on this page, so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and to whom we will disclose it. We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time.
Security Policy:
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Whenever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
We protect your information offline as well. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personal information are kept in a secure environment.
Copyright Policy:
All content included as part of this site, the compilation, collection, arrangement and assembly of all content such as text, logos, trademarks, graphics, and button icons, is the property of Limited Papers or its content suppliers, and is protected by U.S. and international copyright and trademark laws.  All software used in this site is the property Limited Papers or its software suppliers and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All such content and software may be used as a shopping resource. Any other use, such as reproducing, distributing or commercially exploiting such content and software, is strictly prohibited.
Submissions:
Limited Papers does not want to receive confidential, proprietary or trade secret information through this web site (excluding information related to any order you submit). Please note that, (excluding personal customer, order and payment information which is subject to our privacy policy set forth below) any information, materials, suggestions, ideas or comments sent to Limited Papers will be deemed non-confidential, and, by submitting any such information, you are granting Limited Papers an irrevocable and unrestricted license to use, modify, reproduce, transmit, display and distribute such information, materials, suggestions, ideas or comments for any purpose whatsoever. However, we will not use your name in connection with any such materials, information, suggestions, and ideas or comments unless we first obtain your permission or otherwise are required by law to do so.
Links to 3rd party sites:
This site may be linked to other sites which are not maintained by Limited Papers, Limited Papers has not reviewed all of the other sites linked to this site and is not responsible for any off-site pages or any other sites linked to this site. The inclusion of any link to other sites does not imply endorsement by Limited Papers of such sites. Linking to any other site pages or other sites is at your own risk.
Disclaimer:
This site is presented by Limited Papers on an “as is” basis. Limited Papers makes no representations or warranties of any kind express or implied, as to the operation of this site, or the information, content, materials or merchandise offered for sale or included on this site. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Limited Papers disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. Subject to the policies expressed above, Limited Papers will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use of this site or the purchase of merchandise from this site (including but not limited to, direct, indirect, incidental, punitive and consequential damages), even if Limited Papers has been advised of the possibility of such damages.
This site is created and controlled by Limited Papers in the State of New York, USA. Use of this site will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New York without giving effect to any conflict of law principles. By purchasing merchandise through this site, you agree that the offer and sale of such merchandise takes place in, and will be governed exclusively by the laws of, the State of New York without giving effect to any conflict of law principles. You also agree that any legal or equitable claim against Limited Papers arising from or related to your purchase must be brought in the city, state or federal courts located in Kings County, New York.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800 797-7022 or by using our contact form.
If you have any questions about this Privacy notice, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us by sending a letter to:
Limited Papers
Attn: Policy Notice
249 Astor St.
